[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Many Asian actors feel like they are___on Australian television shows.",
        "answer": "under-represented"
    },
    {
        "question": "The men were in the forest trying to___the bear that had been eating their sheep.",
        "answer": "trap"
    },
    {
        "question": "I tried my best to make a good presentation, but the teacher told me it just wasn't___enough to get a good grade.",
        "answer": "sufficient"
    },
    {
        "question": "The President said that reducing pollution was her___responsibility.",
        "answer": "governmental"
    },
    {
        "question": "Our teacher refused to talk about her___process as to who got high grades, and who didn't.",
        "answer": "decision-making"
    },
    {
        "question": "Many people don't know that in the US, judges are often___to their positions.",
        "answer": "elected"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cry of a baby is something that most parents can't___.",
        "answer": "ignore"
    },
    {
        "question": "He had no___of how fast he was driving.",
        "answer": "awareness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Covid is a serious problem that some countries___with by keeping their borders closed.",
        "answer": "dealt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pizza is loved by college students___.",
        "answer": "globally"
    },
    {
        "question": "I put two cups of sugar in the cake mix, do you think it will be___?",
        "answer": "sufficient"
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher said we had already___with this problem in an earlier class.",
        "answer": "dealt"
    },
    {
        "question": "The___met all night in order to finish the new budget for the country.",
        "answer": "legislators"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is often a lot of income___between workers in the north and south parts of the country.",
        "answer": "inequality"
    },
    {
        "question": "The___of class time we have to work together just isn't enough to finish the assignment.",
        "answer": "percentage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finding jobs for everyone is a difficult___problem for the government to try and solve.",
        "answer": "social"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the hardest parts of being a leader is___. You have to consider many different things when you create new rules.",
        "answer": "decision-making"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before you got to Europe, you should plan what kind of___you'll be taking between the different countries.",
        "answer": "transportation"
    },
    {
        "question": "It seemed___that the parents paid for both of their children's educations equally.",
        "answer": "equitable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Japan has some of the cleanest___in the world.",
        "answer": "subways"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dogs are___animals that enjoy being around people.",
        "answer": "social"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thanks to your hard work, many___families will be able to live better lives.",
        "answer": "underprivileged"
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists are telling us that sleep is___important to our overall health.",
        "answer": "extremely"
    },
    {
        "question": "After the factory closed, most of the people in the town were___.",
        "answer": "unemployed"
    },
    {
        "question": "The university was in the news because of the___of what kinds of students it allowed to study there.",
        "answer": "inequality"
    },
    {
        "question": "You'd better start reading that novel for class now, because it's___long, and it will take you a while to finish all of it.",
        "answer": "extremely"
    },
    {
        "question": "My roommate hasn't taken a shower in three weeks, and it's getting hard to___his odor.",
        "answer": "ignore"
    },
    {
        "question": "The judge said he couldn't think of solution that would be___to both parents.",
        "answer": "equitable"
    },
    {
        "question": "The pandemic has raised___of the need to take better care or our health.",
        "answer": "awareness"
    },
    {
        "question": "I want to work for a group that helps___children after I graduate college.",
        "answer": "underprivileged"
    },
    {
        "question": "The people___a whole new group of people to run their city.",
        "answer": "elected"
    },
    {
        "question": "Men are becoming___in colleges each year. Fewer and fewer of them are choosing to go to university after finishing high school.",
        "answer": "under-represented"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are a large number of female___in the government this year.",
        "answer": "legislators"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not graduating from high school can___you into a life of low-paying jobs.",
        "answer": "trap"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a new job, but I can't get to it because there isn't any___to the company's office.",
        "answer": "transportation"
    },
    {
        "question": "The company was known___for its high-quality products.",
        "answer": "globally"
    },
    {
        "question": "The government takes a___of my salary as taxes each month.",
        "answer": "percentage"
    },
    {
        "question": "You'll have to hurry home because the___will all close soon.",
        "answer": "subways"
    },
    {
        "question": "I don't think I have the right personality for___work. I would rather be a businessperson instead.",
        "answer": "governmental"
    }
]